Prepare tuna can!
Squeeze oil as much as you can ^^
Wring tofu out smashing it ^^
You throw away tofu container right before? Sorry :( Bring it back haha
Press down prepared ingredients right before on the container ^^
It is nervous time! Hu ha Hu ha ! Take a deep breath for a moment!
Flip it over at once !!!!!!!
Let it stay until one side of it cook well at low heat ^^
Then flip it over when one side of it almost cooked ^^ It is better that beginners use wide enough spatula :)
Oh my god!  It is okay haha. I will get stitches of this ^^
You can flip it over again like this to put this on the plate.
Ta-da !!!!!!!
You can add some sauces on it depending on your flavor
Thank you for watching this video ^^ It would be really helpful if you click subscription and likes buttons :)